n-ix.com 2019-08-05

# Privacy Policy - N-iX

### **Introduction**

N-iX LLC and its affiliated companies (herein together referred to as N-iX) respect and realize importance of protecting your privacy, and N-iX is committed to protecting your privacy rights to the fullest possible extent.

By reading and accepting this N-iX Privacy Policy you understand and give your consent to be bound by it.

### **Safety of Your Personal Information**

We may have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you, information we receive from your use of our website (www.n-ix.com) and information we have obtained about you from public available sources. This may include your name, phone number, email address, type of inquiry, website, company, job title, data on our communications with you, other general analytic data and other additional information you provide to us. We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us as well as to let you know about other products and services that we offer, and products and services that our partners offer. This may take the form of emails, phone calls, remarketing and ad campaigns, newsletters or any other form of marketing in the future.

N-iX collects this information in order to support your participation in the activities you select. N-iX also uses information that you provide for the following purposes:

  * To communicate with you
  * To improve user experience
  * To improve our site
  * To improve customer service
  * To administer the contractual relationship, if it is necessary

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our website. Personal data that we process for any purpose(s) will not be kept for longer that is necessary for that purpose(s), including compliance with legal requirements.

We may share your information with the following recipients: our affiliated companies, professional advisers, third party providers, partners, contractors, employees for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or notified to you. In addition, we may share your information with competent law enforcement bodies, regulatory, government agencies, courts or other third parties where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another person.

### **Information tracking**

This website may automatically collect information about you in several ways, which includes tracking your activities through your IP address, computer settings, most-recently visited URL, operating system, date and time, your preferences and choices and saved options subject to your browser settings.This website uses your IP Address to help diagnose problems with its server, and to administer website.

### **Third Party Links**

Our website may contain links to third party websites. N-iX LLC shall not be held responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites.

### **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy by publishing a new version on this website from time to time at our sole discretion. Any changes we make to this Privacy Policy will be posted on the website so that you are always aware of what information we gather, how we might use that information and under which circumstances we may disclose it.

### **Cookie Policy**

As most Websites, our Website uses cookies to help us provide you with the best possible browsing experience.

Cookies are chosen data stored on your computer which help us to immediately recognize your PC at your next visit. Cookies automatically (i.e., not by registration) compile collective non-personal data (such as Internet browsers, operating systems, domain names, website visits, average visit time, pages per visit).

There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.

By accepting this N-iX Privacy Policy and continuing to browse this website you agree to our use of cookies. You can always delete or disable cookies in your Internet browser settings, asking it to erase all cookies from your computer’s hard drive, stop all cookies or to be noticed before a cookie is stored.

In order to disable the cookie feature on your browser, please follow the links below:

### **Remarketing**

Cookies are also used to display remarketing advertisements, based upon the user’s previous visits to[  https://www.n-ix.com/, ](https://www.n-ix.com/) across the internet.

Remarketing advertisements are displayed through the Google Display Advertising Network. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies at any time by visiting the [ Google Ads Preferences Manager.  
](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/)

### **Your Privacy Rights**

Your principal privacy rights include the right to access, right to rectification, right to erasure, right to restrict processing, right to object to processing, right to data portability, right to complain to a supervisory authority and right to withdraw consent.

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect, you can submit a request to see this information and even have it corrected, ported to you or deleted.

At any time you may withdraw your consent or object to data processing by contacting us at **dataprotection@n-ix.com**. In case you withdraw your consent it will not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us at [dataprotection@n-ix.com ](mailto:dataprotection@n-ix.com). Your information we use for purposes explained in this N-iX Privacy Policy will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to have your information stored.

### **Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at dataprotection@n-ix.com or by phone +380 322 295 767.

N-iX LLC is registered under the laws of Ukraine and our principal place of business is at 32 Storozhenka St. Lviv, 79018 Ukraine.
